KHUSHBOO CHANDNANI

khushboochandnani21@gmail.com | (317)-720-5928 | Portfolio | LinkedIn | Github

CAREER SUMMARY

Eager and Passionate UX/UI Designer having 2+ years of experience in creating effective and innovative interactive designs. Being an engineer, I have a creative problem-solving approach to create fine user experiences. Persistence, curiosity and an obsessive attention to detail having an ability to work in team environments define me.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Indiana University (IUPUI)

User Experience Research Assistant 08/30/2022 - Ongoing

- Researching on the changes in body temperature system of pre-mature babies and designing the mobile
 app that gets integrated with the monitoring device.
- Performing user survey's and user interviews to understand the feedback on usability of app at IU School of Medicine.

Ernst and Young

Associate Business Consultant 11/23/2020 - 07/07/2022

- Played a critical role in supporting statutory audits of different clients belonging to the financial services domain.
- Tested various ITGCs and ITACs within the client's IT environment to validate if the underlying risk is being mitigated or not.

Fitpeo Org.

Product Designer (Freelancer) 02/16/2022 - 05/16/2022

- Designed an integrated platform that allows healthcare providers to connect with patients and provide them with remote care.
- Performed user surveys and interviews to identify usability and accessibility issues.
- Designed CCM, RPM, BHI modules to monitor patient's health including Vital sign monitoring, telehealth
 via video chat, appointment scheduling, and 24-hour access to their dedicated health care team.

The Indian Navy

Lead UX/UI Designer (Freelancer) 08/15/2021 - 11/14/2021

- Shifted two major paper-based systems to digitized products eB&D Spares and Signals Management System.
- Gathered the stakeholder's requirements and designed interactive software for the naval team to manage their expectations and is easier to be used by the sailors and auditors on board the ship.

Government of Sierra Leone

UX/UI Designer (Freelancer) 03/07/2021 - 04/27/2021

- Designed COVID19 app for Government of Sierra Leone country showing graphical representation of global case statistics and features showing news updates, request for test, report a case, self test and finding hotspot areas.
- Researched on various competitors, performed quantitative analysis, identified new feature sets, prototyped and visualized large amount of data making the interface usable for the citizens.

EDUCATION

2022 - Ongoing Pursuing Master's in Human Computer Interaction

Indiana University - Purdue University Indianapolis (IUPUI)

2016 - 2020 Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology

Vivekanand Education Society's Institute Of Technology

SKILLS

DESIGN METHODS User Research, User Interviews, User Personas, Storyboarding, User Flow Diagrams, Prototyping

TOOLS Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop, Power BI, Excel, PowerPoint

TECHNOLOGIES HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, PHP, SQL